得了，那没什么大不了的
Would you let it go? It's not a big deal.
没什么？简直是太神奇了
ROSS: Not a big deal? It's amazing.
只要把手伸进去弄一弄
You just reach in, there's one little maneuver, and bam!
一件胸罩 就直接从袖子里出来
A bra. Right out the sleeve.
据我所知，这种事
As far as I'm concerned...
男人根本就做不来，对吧？
...there is nothing a guy can do that comes close. Right?
拜托！你们男人可以站着小便
Come on! You guys can pee standing up.
我们可以吗？ 好，我会试试
We can? Okay, I'm trying that.
知道我想到什么了吗？
You know what blows my mind?
女人随时可以看到胸部
Women can see breasts anytime they want.
只要往下一看 就在那里
You just look down, and there they are.
真不懂你们哪有办法 专心做事
How you get any work done is beyond me.
我知道了…我不懂男人怎能 做出许多残忍的事情…
What I don't get is the way guys can do so many mean things...
却完全不在乎
...and then not even care.
多重性高潮！
Multiple orgasms!
《老友记》  第一季  第5集  东德进口的洗衣粉
Friends S01E05: The One with the East German Laundry Detergent
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
（中央咖啡厅）
周六夜 大日子！
So Saturday night, the big night.
约会的日子！ 周六夜，周六夜！
Date night! Saturday night. Saturday night!
- 你没节目，对吧？ - 一个也没有！
- No plans, huh? - Not a one.
连跟珍妮丝分手的计划也没有？
Not even, say, breaking up with Janice?
（制片：塔德·史帝文斯）
对，对，闭嘴
Oh, right, right. Shut up.
钱德，没人喜欢跟别人分手
Chandler, nobody likes breaking up with someone.
（编剧：杰夫·葛林斯坦  杰夫·史特劳斯）
- 只是你非做不可 - 我知道，不过真的很难
- You just gotta do it. - I know. But it's just so hard.
（导演：帕蜜拉·佛莱曼）
你就跟她坐在一起 她浑然不觉
You're sitting with her. She has no idea what's happening.
终于你鼓起勇气 开始行动
You finally get up the courage to do it.
当你把纸条传给她时 气氛很僵
There's that awkward moment when you've handed her the note.
你干嘛非得跟她分手不可？
Why do you have to break up with her?
像个男人，不要再打电话就好了
Be a man. Just stop calling.
如果你需要的话 我可以跟你一起做
If you want, I'll do it with you.
谢谢，不过她会觉得 我们在联合起来对付她
Thanks, but she'd feel like we were ganging up on her.
不，我是说是你甩珍妮丝 我甩东尼
I mean you break up with Janice. I'll break up with Tony.
你要跟东尼分手？
You're breaking up with Tony?
他很甜，不过已经不好玩了
I know. He's sweet, but it's just not fun anymore.
我不晓得原因在于我 或在于他的绝食
I don't know if it's me or his hunger strike. I don't know.
你们还要点些什么吗？
Does anybody want anything else?
对了，你们上礼拜有一种有很好吃的 核桃巧克力的蛋糕或派的一种…
Yeah. Last week you had a wonderful nutty, chocolate-y, kind of cake-y pie thing that...
不用了，我不饿
Nothing. I'm fine.
（《自行车》）
怎么了？ 干嘛苦瓜脸？
What's the matter? Why so scrunchie?
我爸要给我一辆宾士敞篷
It's my father. He wants to give me a Mercedes convertible.
那家伙，真是令我火大
That guy, he burns me up.
对，是宾士 只要我搬回家去
Yeah, well, it's a Mercedes if I move back home.
真讨厌！ 他还叫我〝小姑娘〞
It was horrible! He called me "young lady."
我爸爸那样叫我时 我也很气
Ooh, I hate when my father calls me that.
他是否又念些 〝你不可能办到〞之类的？
Did he give you that whole "You're not up to this" thing again?
我听到的是加长版 有一句不断重复的副歌是…
Yeah, I got the extended disco version with three choruses of:
〝靠你自己是不可能成功的〞
"You'll never make it on your own."
哦 噢
Uh-huh, uh-huh
嘿，乔伊
Hi, Joey.
哦，我的天！安琪拉！
Oh, my God. Angela.
哇！被你甩掉 对她显然是好事
Wow. Being dumped by you obviously agrees with her.
- 你要过去吗？ - 不
- Are you gonna go over there? - No.
好，不
Yeah. No.
可以，不过时候未到 我不想显得太饥渴
Okay, but not yet. I don't wanna seem too eager.
一下下、两下下…
One Mississippi, two Mississippi...
三下下 这样似乎就很酷了
...three Mississippi. That seems pretty cool.
嘿，安琪拉
Hey, Angela.
乔伊
Joey.
你看起来很性感
You look good.
那是因为我穿着一件 特别强调胸部的衣服
Because I'm wearing a dress that accents my boobs.
可不是吗
You don't say.
那，瑞秋，你晚上有何计划？
So, Rachel, what are you doing tonight?
晚上可精彩了 我跟摩妮卡要去自助洗衣店
Big glamour night. Me and Monica at Launderama.
噢
Oh.
你想听一件诡异的巧合吗？
You wanna hear a freakish coincidence?
猜猜还有谁也会去？
Guess who's doing laundry there too?
- 谁 - 我
- Who? - Me.
这样还不够清楚吗？
Was that not clear?
何不…？
Hey, why don't...?
我何不加入你们两个人的行列？
Why don't I just join you both there?
你住的大楼 不就有一间洗衣室？
Don't you have a laundry room in your building?
对
Yes.
我那里有一间洗衣室
I do have a laundry room in my building.
不过，那里有老鼠出没
Um... But there's a rat problem.
他们显然对烘干机的芳香片 很有兴趣
Apparently, they're attracted to the dryer sheets.
他们进去的时候都还好好的 出来的时候就…
They're going in fine, but they're coming out all...
蓬蓬的了
...fluffy.
总之，七点左右好吗？
Anyway, 7-ish?
当然
Sure.
少来，我现在跟鲍柏在一起了
Forget it, Joey. I'm with Bob now.
鲍柏？鲍柏是谁？
Bob? Who the hell's Bob?
鲍柏很棒
Bob is great.
他很聪明、见过世面 而且有正当工作
He's smart, he's sophisticated, and he has a real job.
你一个月试镜三次 就说自己是演员，鲍柏则…
You go on three auditions a month and you call yourself an actor. But Bob...
拜托！我们在一起时很快乐
Come on. We were great together.
不只是享乐的时候 比如说，谈话的时候也不错
And not just at the fun stuff, but, like, talking too.
抱歉，你说过〝我们就当朋友〞
Sorry, Joey. You said, "Let's just be friends."
你猜结果呢？
So guess what?
- 怎样？ - 我们就只是朋友
- What? - We're just friends.
好吧，好吧
Fine. Fine.
今天我们四个人 何不一块吃饭？就朋友嘛
So why don't the four of us go out and have dinner tonight? You know, as friends.
哪四个〝我们〞？
What "four of us"?
你跟鲍柏 我跟我的女朋友…
You and Bob, and me and my girlfriend, um...
摩妮卡
...Monica.
摩妮卡，我告诉你 这家伙很适合你
JOEY: Monica, I'm telling you, this guy is perfect for you.
甭想！自从你那个打嗝天王亲戚后 我就不再相信你了
Forget it! Not after your cousin who could belch the alphabet.
拜托，这家伙很棒 他叫鲍柏，他是安琪拉的…
Come on, this guy's great. His name's Bob. He's Angela's...
兄弟
...ahem, brother.
他很聪明又见过世面…
He's smart, he's sophisticated...
而且他有正当工作
...and he has a real job.
我一个月试镜三次 就说我是个演员，不过他是…
Me, I go on three auditions a month and call myself an actor, but Bob is...
- 老天爷啊 - 干嘛？
- Oh, God, help us. - What?
丑陋裸男在铺厨房地砖
Ugly Naked Guy is laying kitchen tile.
呕
BOTH: Ew!
我是在请你帮忙
Look, I'm asking a favor here.
只要我帮她兄弟这个忙
I'm thinking if I do this for her brother...
安琪拉也许就会回到我身边
...maybe Angela will come back to me.
你干嘛？ 你的女朋友加起来有几卡车
What's going on here? You go out with tons of girls.
我知道，不过…
I know, but...
我犯了一个大错 我不该跟她分手的
Look, I made a huge mistake. I never should've broke up with her.
你帮帮我好吗？拜托？
Will you help me? Please?
好，再见
Okay. Bye.
摩妮卡不去了 只剩下我跟瑞秋
Monica's not coming. It's just gonna be me and Rachel.
等等，你这黄鼠狼 你仔细思考过了吗？
Hold on there, camper. You sure you've thought this through?
只是去洗衣服 不太需要用到大脑吧
It's laundry. The thinking through is pretty minimal.
只有你跟瑞秋？ 只有你们两个？
It's just you and Rachel? Just the two of you?
这是约会 你们要去约会了
This is a date. You're going on a date.
恩-啊
Nuh-uh.
呀-哈
Yeah-huh.
你觉得呢？
What are you saying?
我该再刮一下胡子 或拿瓶酒过去吗?
I should shave again? Pick up some wine? What?
嗯，你也许需要 再考虑一下你的脏内裤
Well, you may wanna rethink the dirty underwear.
这将是她首次目睹你的内裤 你希望是脏脏的吗？
It's the first time she'll see your underwear. You want it to be dirty?
不希望
No.
还有柔衣精呢？
And the fabric softener?
好，我的柔衣精又碍到谁了？
Okay, okay. Now, what is wrong with my Snuggles?
怎样？这代表我是一个 感性、温暖的男人
What? It says I'm a sensitive, warm kind of guy.
知道吗？就像一只毛绒绒的小熊
You know, like a little fuzzy bear.
我在路上再买别的好了
I can pick something else up on the way.
（餐厅）
谢谢
MONICA: Thank you.
这个鲍柏长什么样子？ 他是高还是矮？
So what does this Bob guy look like? Is he tall, short?
对
Yep.
到底怎样？
Which?
什么怎样？
Which what?
你也没见过鲍柏，对吧？
You've never met Bob, have you?
没有，不过…
No, but...
老天，这家伙搞不好长得很…
For all we know, he could be horribly...
嘿，乔伊！
Hey, Joey
很迷人 我不再多说了
Horribly attractive. I'll be shutting up now.
他们人呢？人呢？
Where are they? Where are they?
太棒了，我们从来没有 单独做过什么事，就我们两个
This is nice. We never do anything, just the two of us.
太好了，也许我们明天 可以租辆车去撞一些小狗
That's great. Maybe tomorrow we can rent a car, run over some puppies.
我才不要
Ew. I don't wanna do that.
- 开始了 - 祝分手顺利
- Here we go. - Have a good breakup.
- 嘿，珍妮丝 - 我的天，我很高兴你打电话给我
- Hey, Janice. - My God, I am so glad you called me.
我今天真是衰到家了
I had the most supremely awful day.
那可不妙
That's not good.
请送意式浓缩咖啡跟拿铁过来 好吗？
Can I get an espresso and a latte over here, please?
我们拿到那些蔬菜照片的样本了
We got the proofs from that photo shoot with the vegetables.
拍得很糟
They sucked.
我干脆下午翘班去血拼
I blew off the rest of the afternoon. I went shopping.
我给你买…
And I got you...
我在找，我在找
JANICE: I'm looking. I'm looking.
我在找
I'm looking.
- 我给你买… - 什么？
- I got you... - What?
- 什么？ - 你给我买了什么了？
- What? - What did you get me there?
我给你…
I got you...
买了这个
...these.
《鹿兄鼠弟》的鹿兄袜
Bullwinkle socks.
- 真好 - 我知道你已经有鼠弟的了
- That's so sweet. - I knew you had the Rockys.
你可以穿鹿兄配鹿兄
So you could wear Bullwinkle and Bullwinkle...
或鼠弟配鼠弟，或混着穿
...or wear Rocky and Rocky, or you can mix and match.
糜鹿跟飞天鼠
Moose and squirrel.
随你搭配
Whatever you want.
我还要一杯义式浓缩咖啡 你还要拿铁吗？
I'm gonna get another espresso. More latte?
不用了
No.
不，我还在努力的喝这一杯
No, I'm still working on mine.
就这样？
That's it?
真的很困难 对
Yeah, it was really hard.
那个拥抱感觉很残酷 对
Yeah, the hug looked pretty brutal.
你又不在场
Okay, you weren't there.
（自助洗衣店  自助或代洗）
别挡路，让开，让开！
WOMAN: Coming through! Move! Move!
不好意思！我在用这部机器
Excuse me! I was kind of using that machine.
对，嗯，现在你好像没在用了
Yeah, well, now you're kind of not.
不过我已经有保留 我把篮子放在上面了
But I saved it. I put my basket on top.
- 真对不起，这是你的篮子？ - 对
- I'm sorry. Is that your basket? - Yes.
很漂亮 可惜的是，我没看到洗衣粉！
It's really pretty. Unfortunately, I don't see suds!
什么？
What?
没有洗衣粉就不能保留，好吗？
No suds, no save, okay?
- 什么事？ - 嗨
- What's going on? - Hi.
没什么，那个讨厌的女人 抢了我的洗衣机
Nothing. This horrible woman just took my machine.
你的篮子有放在上面吗？
Was your basket on top?
- 有，不过没放洗衣粉 - 那又怎样？
- Yeah, but there were no suds. - So?
就是…没洗衣粉就不算保留
You know, no suds, no save.
没洗衣粉就不…不好意思
No suds, no... Excuse me.
等一下！
Hold on a second!
这是我朋友的洗衣机
This is my friend's machine.
嘿，嘿，嘿! 她的东西没放在里面
Hey, hey, hey! Her stuff wasn't in it!
嘿，嘿，嘿! 你明知规矩不是那样的！
Hey, hey, hey! That's not the rule, and you know it!
好，戏演完了
All right. Show's over.
没什么好看的了
Nothing to see here.
好，我们开始洗衣服了
Okay. Let's do laundry.
太厉害了！ 我连不是我点的汤都不敢退还
That was amazing! I can't even send back soup.
那是因为你是如此甜美、温柔…
Well, that's because you're such a sweet, gentle...
你有…？
Do you, uh?
哦，嘿，你一定需要洗衣粉
Oh, hey. You must need detergent.
- 那是什么？ - 超白牌洗衣粉
- What's that? - Überweiss.
是新的，德国货 超强力！
It's new. It's German. It's extra tough!
瑞秋，你这些要分开吗？
Rach, do you...? Are you gonna separate those?
哦，天
Oh, God. Ugh.
我很洗衣白痴，对不对？
Am I being like a total laundry spaz?
我是否该把上衣跟裤子 分别放入不同的洗衣机？
Am I supposed to use one machine for shirts and another for pants?
你从来没洗过衣服吗？
Have you...? Have you never done this before?
哦，我是没有啦 可是我认识一些洗过衣服的人
Well, not myself. But I know other people that have.
好，被你逮到了 我是个洗衣处女
Okay. You caught me. I'm a laundry virgin.
不要害怕 我会慢慢来
Don't worry. I'll use the gentle cycle.
好吧
Okay...
基本上，你得把所有白色的 放在一部机器里
Basically, you wanna use one machine for all your whites.
白色的，好
Whites. Okay.
- 有颜色的放入另一部 - 有颜色的
- A whole other machine for your colors. - Colors.
还要第三部洗你的…
And then a third for your, uh...
贴身衣物 也就是你的胸罩…
...delicates. And that would be your bras...
你的小内裤之类的
...and your underpanty things.
这些是白色的棉质内裤
Okay, well, these are white cotton panties.
是要跟白色的衣物放一起 还是跟贴身衣物呢？
Would they go with whites or with delicates?
这得靠你自由心证了
That would be a judgment call.
他好可爱！
He's so cute!
你们在哪里长大的？
So where did you guys grow up?
- 布鲁克林高地 - 克里夫兰
- Brooklyn Heights. - Cleveland.
哈 呵呵呵
Ha. Heh, heh, heh.
- 怎么会这样？ - 我的天！
- How did that happen? - Oh, my God!
怎么了？
What?
我突然有一种…
I suddenly had the feeling I was...
往下掉的感觉
...falling.
现在没有了
But I'm not.
你跟安琪拉在一起，是吧？
So you and Angela, huh?
没错，就是这样
Yep. Pretty much.
- 你是个幸运的男人 - 是啊
- You're a lucky man. - Yeah.
知道我最想念她哪里吗？
You know what I miss the most about her?
她吃东西时发出的 可爱的小噪音
That cute nibbley noise she makes when she eats.
就像一只快乐的小松鼠…
Like a happy little squirrel...
或是黄鼠狼
...or a weasel.
我没注意到
I never really noticed.
哦，有 有，你要注意听
Oh, yeah, yeah. Listen for it.
摩妮卡 摩妮卡很正
Monica. Monica is great.
对，她是啊
Yeah. Yeah, she is.
不过，不会长久
But it's not gonna last.
对我而言 她在床上需求太多了
She's too much for me in bed.
嘿咻方面
Sexually.
我得告诉你 鲍柏超棒的
I've gotta tell you, Bob is terrific.
对，说的可不是？
Yeah, isn't he?
能遇到一个聪明、有趣
It's so great to meet a guy who's smart and funny...
成熟度超过八岁的男人真好
...and has an emotional age beyond 8.
还有你知道吗？ 他在床上的表现让人难以置信！
You know what else? He's unbelievable in bed!
哇
Wow!
我哥连他几岁失去童贞 都没告诉过我
My brother never even told me when he lost his virginity.
呵
Huh.
那很好啊
That's nice.
（中央咖啡厅）
你可以的 就像扯下OK绷一样
You can do this. It's like pulling off a Band-Aid.
动作快点 伤口就会露出来了
Just do it really fast, and then the wound is exposed.
快！快去！
Go! Go!
珍妮丝
Janice...
嗨，珍妮丝
Hi, Janice.
好，开始了 我想我们不该再交往下去了
Okay, here we go. I don't think we should go out anymore.
珍妮丝
Janice.
好的
All right.
好吧
Well...
好，你说了
Well, there you go.
停，停，停
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
我知道说来有点蠢…
RACHEL: Okay, I know this is gonna sound really stupid...
不过我觉得 如果我今天能成功…
...but I feel that if I can do this...
如果我真的能洗我自己的衣服…
...if I can actually do my own laundry...
这世上就没有我办不到的事了
...there isn't anything I can't do.
我倒觉得 这句话一点也不蠢
That does not sound stupid to me.
卡萝离开我后 我第一次自己煮东西时…
No, it's like... The first time I had to make dinner for myself after Carol left me...
对不起，我们的时间到了 下一次《罗斯秀》…
I'm sorry, that's all the time we have. Next on Ross...
好
Okay.
- 啊哦 - 干嘛？
- Uh-oh. - What, "uh-oh"?
啊哦…
Uh-oh...
啊哦，衣服洗好了
Uh-oh, the laundry's done.
这是一首歌
It's a song.
我们在洗衣服时唱的
The laundry song that we sing.
啊哦！衣服洗好了
Uh-oh, the laundry's done
怎么了嘛？
What's the matter?
没什么
Nothing. Nothing.
衣服洗好了
The laundry's done
得了，让我看
Come on, show me.
只是你的白衣服里有一只红袜子 所以就…
It's just that you left a red sock in with your whites, and now...
统统变成有点粉红的
...everything's kind of pink. - Oh.
统统变成粉红的？
Everything's pink?
只有那只红袜子例外 还是红的
Except for the red sock, which is still red.
别难过 这种事大家都会遇到的
Don't be upset. It can happen to anyone.
可是这次发生在我身上
But it didn't. It happened to me.
天哪，我会变成 - 只粉红凯蒂猫！
God, I'm gonna look like a big Marshmallow Peep!
我在干什么？
What am I doing? What am I doing?
我爸爸说的对！ 我无法独立
My father's right! I can't live on my own.
我连洗衣服都不会！
I can't even do laundry!
那个超狗气球出状况了
Something went wrong with Underdog...
他们又没办法帮狗头充气
...and they couldn't get his head to inflate.
总之…
So anyway...
狗头就在百老汇上 直直滚下去，对吧？
...his head is, like, flopping down Broadway.
我就在想
And I'm thinking...
这真的是不对劲
...how inappropriate this is.
我的眼里有东西 乔伊，我们到灯光下看看好吗？
I've got something's in my eye. Joey, could we check it in the light, please?
- 哦，我的天！ - 干嘛？
- Oh, my God! - What?
我们坐在同一桌吗？ 简直说是…
Hello! Were we at the same table? It's like...
近亲乱伦
...cocktails in Appalachia.
- 他们很亲密 - 亲密？她的舌头都跑到他耳朵里了
- Come on, they're close. - Close? She's got her tongue in his ear.
你跟罗斯就没胡闹过
Like you've never got a little rambunctious with Ross.
乔伊，这很病态 很恶心、很…
Joey, this is sick. It's disgusting. It's...
这不是真的，对不对？
...not really true, is it?
谁晓得什么才是真的？
Who's to say what's true?
你在想什么？
What were you thinking?
这没什么好得意的，好吗？
Look, I'm not proud of this, okay?
嗯，也许是有一点啦
Well, maybe I am a little.
噢 噢
- Oh. - Ow!
- 我要走了！ - 等一下！
- I'm out of here! - Wait! Come on!
你喜欢他，我要她
You like him. I want her.
他喜欢你
He likes you.
- 真的？ - 对
- Really? - Yeah.
如果我们团结起来 就凭我们二人…
I'm thinking, if we put our heads together, between the two of us...
一定可以拆散他们
...we can break them up.
对不起 真不敢相信我会出这种差错
MONICA: I'm so sorry. I can't believe I did this.
你那个作家诺曼梅勒的故事 让我笑到不行
I just couldn't stop laughing at your Norman Mailer story.
服务生？我们还要一盘鸡翅
Waiter? One more plate of chicken wings over here.
就像这样 我们根本不一样
Here's the thing. It's like we're different.
我是那种乒乒乒的人 你则是砰砰砰
I'm the bing, you're the boom...
哦 噢
JANICE: Ow! - Oh!
- 哦，我的天！ - 噢
- Oh, my God!  - Ow!
- 我很抱歉！ - 噢
- I'm so sorry! - Ow!
你还好吗？
- Are you okay? - Ow!
只是我的隐形眼镜 我的镜片跑了
It's just my lens. It's my lens.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
我打中她的眼睛！ 打中她的眼睛！
I hit her in the eye! I hit her in the eye!
这是史上最差劲的分手！
This is the worst breakup in the history of the world!
哦，我的天！
Oh, my God.
你到底喝了几杯？
How many of those have you had?
我不晓得，一百万杯吧！
I don't know. A million!
钱德，放轻松，放轻松 想想你快乐的时光
Chandler, shh, shh. Easy, easy. Go to your happy place.
啦-啦-啦-啦-啦-啦-啦
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
- 我很好，我很好 - 好吧
- I'm fine, I'm fine. - All right.
我不好，她来了
I'm not fine. Here she comes.
在这里等好吗？呼吸
Wait here, okay? Breathe.
你怎么办到的？
How do you do that?
就像一种天赋
It's like a gift.
以后我们一定要一起分手
We should always, always break up together.
我喜欢！
I'd like that.
衣服干净了 这才是最重要的
ROSS: You got the clothes clean. That's the important part.
我想也是 可惜现在全部看起来都像睡衣
I guess. Except everything looks like jammies now.
对不起
Whoa, I'm sorry.
抱歉，这推车是我们的
Excuse me. We had this cart.
我的腰以前也只有二十四寸 人生总是有得有失
I had a 24-inch waist. You lose things.
好了，别挡我的路
Now, come on. Get out of my way.
对不起，也许我没有说清楚 这推车是我们的
I'm sorry. Maybe I wasn't being clear. This was our cart.
嘿，嘿，嘿! 刚才又没有衣服在推车里！
Hey, hey, hey. There aren't any clothes in it!
嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿 不要乱订规则！
Hey, hey, hey! Quit making up rules!
放手！快，这是我的推车 你知道是我先看到的
Let go! Come on, this is my cart. You know I saw it first.
给我听好，女人 如果你要这推车…
Listen, Mitzi, if you want this cart...
就连我一起推走！
...you're gonna have to take me with it!
赞！你看到了没？
Yes! Did you see that?
你太厉害了
You were incredible.
各位先生、各位女士 看看这位全新的女性
A brand-new woman, ladies and gentlemen.
谢谢，没有你的话 我根本办不到的
I could not have done this without you.
好
ROSS: Okay, um...
干衣机里还有衣服吗？
Uh... More clothes in the dryer?
- 我没事，没事 - 你确定吗？
- I'm fine. I'm fine. - Are you sure?
- 你确定你没事？ - 确定
- Are you sure you're okay? - Yeah.
- 还会痛吗？ - 会
- Does it still hurt? - Yeah.
好主意！你所有的衣服都同色了 我也要这样做
What a neat idea. All your clothes match. I'm gonna do this.
- 嗨
MONICA: Hi!
- 还顺利吗？
PHOEBE: How'd it go?
太棒了！
Excellent!
我们把那一对拆开了 然后各自保留一半
We ripped that couple apart and kept the pieces for ourselves.
好浪漫的故事
What a beautiful story.
对了，我没事
I'm fine, by the way.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
- 钱德呢？ - 他需要一点疗伤的时间
- Where's Chandler? - He needed some time to grieve.
我自由了！我自由了！
CHANDLER: I'm free! I'm free!
应该是复原了
That ought to do it.